How to Rob a Bank is a documentary, crime film directed by Seth Porges.
In this true-crime documentary, a charismatic rebel in 1990s Seattle pulls off an
unprecedented string of bank robberies straight out of the movies.
Scott Scurlock, played by Jordan Burtchett.
Self - Scott's Friend, played by Mark Biggins.
Self - Bank Manager, played by Susan Dodd.
Self - Supervisory Special Agent FBI, played by Ellen Glasser.
Self - Scott's Childhood Friend, played by Steven Harper.
Self - News Anchor, played by Deborah Horne.
How to Rob a Bank is a 2024 American documentary film,
directed by Stephen Robert Morse and Seth Porges.
The film is about Scott Scurlock, also known as The Hollywood Bandit, who
robbed 19 confirmed banks in Seattle between 1992 and 1996.
It premiered on Netflix on June 5, 2024.
The film explores themes of robber, seattle, washington,
bank robber, bank robbery, true crime.